mobilejoomla.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated on Friday, 11 September 2015 12:53 

On our website ("Website" or "Service" or "Mobile Joomla!") you will be asked to provide an email address when registering for an account.

When you register you can choose whether to allow other forum members to contact you by email or private messaging and the type of personal information that is available using your user profile. You can also opt to subscribe to specific forums or threads which means your email address will be used to send information when new posts are made. All email from the forum site includes a link that allows you to opt out from continued subscription to that thread or forum. Forum administrators may use your email address to contact you if necessary.

Occasionally, we may use your email address to inform you about major new updates to Mobile Joomla!. You may always opt-out from this communication. See more below in section Email Marketing.

Your IP address may be used to identify duplicate user accounts (which are forbidden under the forum rules).

Should you choose to edit or create wiki pages your identity is recorded and your username is viewable by those who look at the history of the pages you have worked on. Your IP address may be used to identify possible abuse and may be blocked if abuse is detected.

On Mobile Joomla!, we may use aggregate IP information to help us understand the geographic distribution of those downloading and using Mobile Joomla! and other packages; in order to improve our product and service quality.

On any of the sites with commenting features your name, email address, and IP address will be recorded when you make a comment. This information will not be published or shared with any third parties.

If you make a financial contribution to Mobile Joomla! using the sites, your name, address and other information are collected, but your credit card information is never stored on our sites. Our main payment processor is PayPal, whose privacy policy may be viewed [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside "here").

## Cookies

Cookie information: When you visit this Website, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Mobile Joomla! help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use this Website (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the Website, store your preferences and record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when you return to our site, such as indicating which threads you have read). You may modify your information and preferences by editing your user profile. Cookies also allow us or our business partners to track your usage of the Service over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some or all features of this Website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

## Sharing of information with third parties

With the exception of the issues discussed in this paragraph we do not share your information with third parties. On some sites, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Also, we reserve the right to include a small advertising unit(s) on the mobile sites generated with the Mobile Joomla! extension. In this case, third parties, e.g. Google and other similar ad networks, may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on the mobile site generated with Mobile Joomla! extension. Your own privacy policy must include this information in regard to your mobile site users. You may also disable the ad unit in your Mobile Joomla! installation with the ad removal module available through the Mobile Joomla! website.

Mobile Joomla! may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and for behavioral advertising and to personalize the advertising content you see after you have left this site. 

This Website may use the following services: Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Google Analytics collects data about your traffic via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. 

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising, and opt out of the use of other Google services by visiting Ads Settings ([http://www.google.com/ads/preferences](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)). Also see <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. How Google uses data when you use their partners' sites or apps:  <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners>. 

With Website's permit Google may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to transmit information, optimization, and displaying ads based on you using the Website. You may opt out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting or the transfer of such data for such purposes by Facebook at: [https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/](https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences)

Personally Identifiable Information we may receive from third parties: We may now or in the future receive Personally Identifiable Information about you from third parties. For example, if you access our Site or Service through a third-party connection or log-in, including social networking services such as Google, Facebook, or Twitter, by “following,” “liking,” adding the Mobile Joomla! application, linking your account to the Service, etc., that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to Mobile Joomla!. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook user identification), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Service. 

Your information may be disclosed when we are legally required to by a Finnish court order, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. None of of our websites are structured specifically to attract anyone under 13. However, we recognize that there are Joomla! users and developers under age 13 who may register at one or more of our sites. The privacy policies that apply to all site users also apply to those users under 13.

## Email Marketing

You may also explicitly opt-in to receive information and marketing communication emails from us.

How Can You Stop Receiving Email From Us?

You may opt-out of receiving promotional emails by clicking an unsubscribe link included in each promotional email that we send, or opt-out of all direct marketing by notifying us in writing. If you opt-out, but have registered an account, we may still send you non-promotional customer information, such as important emails regarding our ongoing business relations. 

Collection And Use Of Your Information 

When you opt-in to receive our communication messages, we collect personally identifiable information from you that includes your email address. We will never sell, share, or rent individual personal information with any external parties without your advance written permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to our employees managing this information for the purposes of contacting you, or sending you emails based on your request for information, and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services related to our communications with you. 

How Do We Protect Your Privacy And The Security Of Your Information? 

We use the latest and generally approved security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information collected from you.   
Our email and data storage services comply with the EU Safe Harbor privacy requirements. 

## Future changes

From time to time, we may use user information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

## Questions or comments

If you have questions or comments about this policy or if you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy please contact us at support[a@t]mobilejoomla[d.t]com.
